// JavaScript array for questions and answers:

let questions = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question: "What does Harry accidentally do when he goes to the zoo?",
        answer: "Make the glass in the snake enclosure disappear?",
        options:[
            "Make the glass in the snake enclosure disappear?",
            "Teaches the monkeys to sing?",
            "Turns a flamingo blue?",
            "Turns a meerkat into a football?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question: "What's Harry's mum Lily's surname before she marries Harry's dad?",
        answer: "Evans?",
        options:[
            "Peters?",
            "Smith?",
            "Evans?",
            "Collins?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question: "What's the name of Dudley Dursely's dad?",
        answer: "Vernon?",
        options:[
            "Victor?",
            "Ivan?",
            "Vernon?",
            "Vesuvius?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question: "How many Harry Potter books are there in total?",
        answer: "7?",
        options:[
            "2?",
            "7?",
            "12?",
            "1?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question: "In which year was Harry born?",
        answer: "1980?",
        options:[
            "1991?",
            "1976?",
            "2002?",
            "1980?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question: "What shape scar does Harry have on his forehead?",
        answer: "A lightning bolt?",
        options:[
            "A cat?",
            "A moon?",
            "A fidget spinner?",
            "A lightning bolt?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question: "Who does Harry live with before going to Hogwarts?",
        answer:  "The Dursleys?",
        options:[
            "The Simpsons?",
            "The Menaces?",
            "The Dursleys?",
            "The Sheerans?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question: "What is a 'muggle?",
        answer:  "Someone whose parents aren't magical and can't perform magic?",
        options:[
            "A type of puppet?",
            "A type of cup?",
            "Someone whose parents aren't magical and can't perform magic?",
            "A type of outrageous haircut?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question: "What is the name of Hermione Granger's cat?",
        answer:  "Crookshanks?",
        options:[
            "Bart?",
            "Crookshanks?",
            "Peppa?",
            "Sarah?"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question: "What’s the name of Hogwarts School’s gamekeeper?",
        answer:  "Rubeus Hagrid?",
        options:[
            "Ralph?",
            "Ted?",
            "Homer?",
            "Rubeus Hagrid?"
        ]
    },
];